>> Brian: 越来越近。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Getting closer.
我们有一个问题， setBreed 没有定义。
We have one problem here,
that setBreed's not defined.
所以我们要做的是如果你还记得的话
So what we're gonna do is,
if you remember, we did pass that here and
在末尾使用下拉项， setState 函数，对吗 ?
use drop down at the end,
the setState function, right?
所以我们也要把它抓了
So we're just gonna grab that too.
那么 setBreed ，现在就可以定义了，对，
So setBreed, and
now that'll be defined, right,
从使用的下降到现在
cuz that's coming from the use drop down.
>> Brian: 尚未使用品种，没关系，但是
&gt;&gt; Brian: Not using breed yet,
that's okay, but
我们现在要做的事就是你知道
the thing that we're getting here is hey,
just so you know,
它包含对 setBreeds 的调用，但没有依赖关系列表。
it contains a call to to setBreeds
without a list of dependencies.
这可能导致无限的更新链。
This can lead to an infinite
chain of updates.
所以这里的问题是用 " useEffect " 来声明你的附属关系
So the problem here is with useEffect,
you have to declare your dependencies,
这有点奇怪但只和我待过一段时间
which is kind of an odd phrasing this,
but stick with me for just a second.
>> Brian:useEffect 将立即运行，
&gt;&gt; Brian: useEffect is going to run,
as of right now,
每次被人打电话的时候都很频繁对吧
after every single time that render gets
called, which is too frequently, right?
那就现在
So right now,
每次我把它输入到这里它就会要求一套新的品种
every time I typed into location here,
it would request a new set of breeds.
这显然不正确不是我们想做的对吗
That's obviously incorrect,
it's not what we wanna do, right?
我们只想要在动物更新和第一次更新时请求品种。
We only wanna request breeds when animal
updates, as well as on the first time.
> > 布莱恩: 你可以用 useEffect 来做什么
&gt;&gt; Brian: So
what you can do here with useEffect,
>> 布莱恩: 不如这样
&gt;&gt; Brian: Rather than have this
在每次呈现后运行，我们只能说在这些事情发生变化时才会运行。
run after every single render, we can
say only run when these things change.
所以你要做的就是宣布它所依赖的东西。
So what you do is you declare
the things that it depends on.
所以这要看什么
So here it depends on what?
看动物吧
It depends on animal, right?
如果这些改变，那么我们就需要改变它。
Cuz if that changes then
we need to change it.
所以我们会把动物放在那里， >> 布莱恩: 但是
So we'll put animal there,
&gt;&gt; Brian: But
它在技术上也取决于 setBreed 和 setBreeds。
it also technically depends
on setBreed and setBreeds.
现在你和我都知道这永远不会改变
Now, you and I both know that
that's never gonna change,
但是， >> Brian: ESLint 要求它们仍然
but,
&gt;&gt; Brian: ESLint demands that they still
因为它仍然在技术上取决于它们
be there because it still
technically depends on them.
所以 setBreeds 也一样
So setBreeds as well.
> > 布莱恩: 这些都是什么顺序的，
&gt;&gt; Brian: It doesn't matter
what order these come in,
它只是 React 要检查的依赖关系的列表。
it's just a list of dependencies
that React will check.
如果更改了其中任何一个，请将其重新运行，然后重新运行此效果，
Cuz if any one of these things changed,
rerun this effect after it renders,
否则不要再运行了吧
otherwise, don't run it again, right?
那么现在如果位置发生变化，因为位置不在这里，
So now if location changes,
because location's not in here,
它不会重新运行这种效应
it's not gonna rerun this effect.
> > 布莱恩: 那么让我们来确保这实际上是有用的。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So
let's go make sure this actually works.
如果我刷新这个， >> Brian: 现在，
If I refresh this,
&gt;&gt; Brian: Now,
请注意这一品种已不再灰显
notice that breed is no longer grayed out.
如果我点击这里
If I click on here,
你可以看到它其实有很多新的狗，对吧 ?
you can see that it actually has
a lot of new dogs in it, right?
请注意，如果我开始在此处输入，它不会请求新的品种。
And notice that if I start typing in
here it doesn't request new breeds.
但是如果我把狗换为猫
However, if I changed the dog to be cat,
注意它会在这里灰暗一点
notice that it's gonna gray out here for
just a second.
> > 布莱恩: 速度非常快，但现在注意到它有美国的粗线，
&gt;&gt; Brian: That was very fast, but now
notice here that it has American bobtail,
Calico和 Cornish Rex 之类的
and Calico, and Cornish Rex,
and things like that.
跟小毛茸毛的一样
Same thing with small furry.
我想你可以收养一个小人
I guess you can adopt a skunk.